Press Gang Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Promotion and marketing files, 1975 - 2000; F-184-6; 2.04 m of textual records
  - Author and book promotion files, 1975 - 1999; F-184-6-3; 1.56 m of textual records
    - Richler, Nancy - Throwaway Angels - review correspondence, 1996; F-184-6-3-0-167 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Richler, Nancy - Throwaway Angels - reviews, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-168 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Shimrat, Irit - Call Me Crazy - biography and promotion, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-169 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Shimrat, Irit - Call Me Crazy - review correspondence, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-170 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Shimrat, Irit - Call Me Crazy - reviews, 1997; F-184-6-3-0-171 (Archival box - standard 184-42)
    - Silvera, Makeda - Her Head a Village - promotion, 1992 - 1994; F-184-6-3-0-172 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Silvera, Makeda - Her Head a Village - reviews, 1991 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-173 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Silvera, Makeda - Her Head a Village - tour, 1994; F-184-6-3-0-174 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sara J. David (editors) - Women Look At Psychiatry - advertisement and book information, 1975; F-184-6-3-0-175 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sara J. David (editors) - Women Look At Psychiatry - publicity, 1976; F-184-6-3-0-176 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sara J. David (editors) - Women Look At Psychiatry - review copies, 1976; F-184-6-3-0-177 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sara J. David (editors) - Women Look At Psychiatry - reviews, resource material, 1976; F-184-6-3-0-178 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sara J. David (editors) - Women Look At Psychiatry - desk copy requests, 1976 - 1977; F-184-6-3-0-179 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sara J. David (editors) - Women Look At Psychiatry - promotion, reviews, 1976 - 1977; F-184-6-3-0-180 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sara J. David (editors) - Women Look At Psychiatry - correspondence general, 1977 - 1984; F-184-6-3-0-181 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Stewart, Susan - biography and promotion, 1993; F-184-6-3-0-182 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
      Susan Stewart; Textual records
    - Stonehouse, Cathy - The Words I Know - promotion, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-183 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Stonehouse, Cathy - The Words I Know - review correspondence, 1994 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-184 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Stonehouse, Cathy - The Words I Know - reviews, 1994 - 1995; F-184-6-3-0-185 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Taste This Collective - Boys Like Her - promotion, reviews, 1998; F-184-6-3-0-186 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
      Taste This Collective; Textual records
    - Taste This Collective - correspondence, 1996 - 1997; F-184-6-3-0-187 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Telling It Book Collective - Telling It: Women and Language Across Cultures - promotion, 1990 - 1991; F-184-6-3-0-188 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Telling It Book Collective - Telling It: Women and Language Across Cultures - promotion, reviews, 1991 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-189 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Telling It Book Collective - Telling It: Women and Language Across Cultures - review correspondence, 1990 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-190 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Tulchinsky, Karen X. and C. Allyson Lee, editors - Scenes From the Lesbian Mall - correspondence, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-191 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Tulchinsky, Karen X. - Love Ruins Everything - biography and promotion, 1998; F-184-6-3-0-192 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Tulchinsky, Karen X. - Love Ruins Everything - review correspondence, 1998; F-184-6-3-0-193 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Tulchinsky, Karen X. - Love Ruins Everything - reviews, 1998; F-184-6-3-0-194 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Van de Walle - Falling From Grace - promotion, review copy correspondence, 1984 - 1985; F-184-6-3-0-195 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Van de Walle - Falling From Grace - reviews, 1984 - 1989; F-184-6-3-0-196 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Warland, Betsy - Inversions - promotion, 1991 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-197 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Warland, Betsy - Inversions - reviews, 1991; F-184-6-3-0-198 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Warland, Betsy - Proper Definitions - promotion, 1989 - 1991; F-184-6-3-0-199 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Warland, Betsy - Proper Definitions - promotion, reviews, 1990 - 1996; F-184-6-3-0-200 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Warland, Betsy - tour working file, 1990; F-184-6-3-0-201 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Williams, Jana - Scuttlebutt - promotion, 1990; F-184-6-3-0-202 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Williams, Jana - Scuttlebutt - reviews, 1990 - 1991; F-184-6-3-0-203 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Women's Research Centre - Recollecting Our Lives: Women's Experiences of Childhood Sexual Abuse, 1989 - 1990; F-184-6-3-0-204 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Women's Research Centre - Recollecting Our Lives: Women's Experiences of Childhood Sexual Abuse - promotion, 1989 - 1992; F-184-6-3-0-205 (Archival box - standard 184-43)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkeypuzzle - biography and promotion, 1998; F-184-6-3-0-206 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkeypuzzle - review correspondence, 1998; F-184-6-3-0-207 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkeypuzzle - reviews, 1998 - 1999; F-184-6-3-0-208 (Archival box - standard 184-44)
- Subject files, 1975 - 1999; F-184-7; 33 cm of textual records 18 photographs; General note: photographs are located in file 13.
  Series consists of Press Gang Publishers' general subject files, reflecting their political and professional interests and their links with other organizations in feminist networks and in the publishing industry. Topics and activities documented include censorship, racism, feminist, lesbian and gay issues; liaison with other feminist organizations; ISBN and cataloguing information; and membership in publishers' associations and professional advocacy.
  Records include correspondence, reports and briefs, photographs, Canadian Cataloguing in Publication (CIP) Data Forms, questionnaires, directory listings forms, project proposals, notes and working papers, newsletters, catalogues, articles and other printed reference material.
  - Anti-racism work, 1988 - 1996; F-184-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-45)
  - Book publishing in BC, 1989; F-184-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-45)
  - Censorship, 1991 - 1995; F-184-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-45)
  - CIP / ISBN cataloguing, 1975 - 1997; F-184-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-45)
  - Co-op education programs, 1992 - 1994; F-184-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-45)
  - Fan letters, 1995; F-184-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-45)
  - Feminist Bookstore News, 1998 - 1999; F-184-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-45)
  - Feminist counselling, 1981; F-184-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Feminist, lesbian, gay presses, publishers, 1993 - 1997; F-184-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Finger in the Dyke: In the Life, 1995; F-184-7-0-0-10
  - Lesbian, gay cultural context; Lamda awards, vol. 1, 1993 - 1998; F-184-7-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Lesbian, gay cultural context; Lamda awards, vol. 2, 1993 - 1997; F-184-7-0-0-12 (Newspaper box 184-49)
  - Lesbian, gay cultural context; Lamda awards (photographs), vol. 3, 1993 - 1997; F-184-7-0-0-13 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    18 photographs
  - Letters of outrage, 1996; F-184-7-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Links with alternative presses, 1995; F-184-7-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Match project - Immigrant Fire, vol. 1, 1988 - 1990; F-184-7-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Match project - Immigrant Fire, vol. 2, 1988 - 1990; F-184-7-0-0-17 (Newspaper box 184-49)
  - Publishing associations and directories, 1989 - 1996; F-184-7-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Small Presses Action Network, 1995; F-184-7-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
    Small Presses Action Network; Textual records
  - Spreading the Word project, 1995; F-184-7-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Toronto Women's Bookstore, 1995; F-184-7-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
    Toronto Women's Bookstore; Textual records
  - West Coast Women and Words, 1994 - 1996; F-184-7-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
  - Women's Television Network, 1995; F-184-7-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-46)
    Women's Television Network; Textual records
- Photographs, [ca 1913]–1998, predominant 1988–1998; F-184-8; ca. 160 photographs; Dates of creation: there is one file (file 15) that includes photographs that pre-date 1988.
  Series consists of photographic records relating to Press Gang authors. The photos were primarily used for publicity, promotion, and book jackets. Records include photographs and negatives.
  This series is a group of case files organized by author. The files are arranged alphabetically by author's last name.
  - Press Gang Publishers logo, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
  - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Ellen Adelberg; Currie, Claudia; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Armstrong, Jeanette, 1988; F-184-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Armstrong, Jeannette; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Arnott, Joanne, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Arnott, Joanne; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Baxter, Sheila, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Baxter, Sheila; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Blackbridge, Persimmon; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Blackley, Stuart and Fuller, Janine, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Stuart Blackey; Fuller, Janine; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Bociurkiw, Marusya, 1993; F-184-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Bociurkiw, Marusya; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Brant, Beth, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
  - Chrystos, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Chrystos; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Coyote, Ivan, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Ivan Coyote; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Creese, Gillian, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Gillian Creese; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Crossland, Jackie, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Crossland, Jackie; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Decter, Ann, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Decter, Ann; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - [Diamond, Sarah - Chambermaids and Whistlepants: photographs], [ca 1913] - [ca 1970]; F-184-8-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Diamond, Sara; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Douglas, Marion, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Douglas, Marion; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Dueck, Lynette, 1992; F-184-8-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Dueck, Lynette; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Dykewomon, Elana, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Dykewomon, Elana; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Earle, Zoc, 1998; F-184-8-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Zoc Earle; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Faith, Karlene, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
  - Feminist Book Fair, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
  - Herrington, Barbara, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Herrington, Barbara; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Hryniuk, Angela, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Hryniuk, Angela; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Jones, Lizard, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Jones, Lizard; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Kiss and Tell, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Kiss & Tell Collective; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Kogawa, Joy, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Kogawa, Joy; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Lai, Larissa, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Lai, Larissa; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Lambda awards photographs, 1996; F-184-8-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
  - Lee, Sky, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Lee, Sky; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Maracle, Lee, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Maracle, Lee; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Marlatt, Daphne, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Marlatt, Daphne; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - McLauglin, Karen, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    McLaughlin, Karen; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Mootoo, Shani, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Mootoo, Shani; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Norgate, Sheila, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 184-47)
    Norgate, Sheila; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Profeit-Lablanc, Louise, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-35 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Profeit-LeBlanc, Louise; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Richler, Nancy, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-36 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Shimrat, Irit, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-37 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Silvera, Makeda, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-38 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Silvera, Makeda; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Stonehouse, Cathy, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-39 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Stonehouse, Cathy; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Strong-Boag, Veronica, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-40 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Strong-Boag, Veronica; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Taste This, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-41 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Taste This Collective; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Tulchinsky, Karen, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-42 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Tulchinsky, Karen; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Vancouver Sath, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-43 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Warland, Betsy, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-44 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Warland, Betsy; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Williams, Jana, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-45 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Jana Williams; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Women's Research Centre authors, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-46 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Women's Research Centre; Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Wong, Rita, [199-?]; F-184-8-0-0-47 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Wong, Rita; Textual records; Photographic materials
- Published books, 1977 - 1999; F-184-9; 146 books (80 titles); Physical description: some titles exist in multiple editions, including translations into other languages. Each separate edition has been registered as a separate item. For most titles, Press Gang retained two copies.
  Series consists of the archive copies of books published by Press Gang. Two copies of each book have been retained where possible.
  Books are arranged alphabetically by author.
  An item list is available.
  - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie, editors - In Conflict with The Law: Women and the Canadian Justice System, 1993; F-184-9-0-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item1.
  - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - Two Few to Count: Candian Women In Conflict with The Law, October 1987; F-184-9-0-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item3.
  - Arnott, Joanne - Breasting the Waves: On Writing and Healing, 1995; F-184-9-0-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item5.
  - Arnott, Joanne - Ma MacDonald (Toronto: Women's Press), 1993; F-184-9-0-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item7.
  - Arnott, Joanne - My Grass Cradle, December 1992; F-184-9-0-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item8.
  - Arnott, Joanne - Wiles of Girlhood, 1991; F-184-9-0-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item10.
  - Bank Book Collective - An Account to Settle: The Story of the United Bank Workers (SORWUC), 1979; F-184-9-0-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Bank Book Collective; Service, Office, and Retail Workers Union of Canada; Textual records
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item12.
  - Baxter, Sheila - Still Raising Hell: Poverty, Activism and Other True Stories, 1997; F-184-9-0-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item14.
  - Beckylane - Where The Rivers Join: A Personal Account of Healing from Ritual Abuse, 1995; F-184-9-0-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item16.
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon and Sheila Gilhooley - Still Sane, 1985; F-184-9-0-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-50)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item18.
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Prozac Highway, 1997; F-184-9-0-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item19.
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Prozac Highway (London: Marion Boyars Publishers), 1999; F-184-9-0-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item20.
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook: A True Story with Lies (sample copy, entire book reprinted), 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item21.
  - Bociurkiw, Marusya - The Woman Who Loved Airports, 1994; F-184-9-0-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item22.
  - Brant, Beth - Food and Spirits, 1991; F-184-9-0-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item23.
  - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike (first printing), August 1982; F-184-9-0-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item25.
  - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike (second run), 1982; F-184-9-0-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item27.
  - Briskin, Linda and Maureen Fitzgerald - Quand les fées font la grève (Les Editions Heritage Inc.), 1986; F-184-9-0-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Briskin, Linda; Maureen Fitzgerald; Textual records
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item29.
  - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman, July 1981; F-184-9-0-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item31.
  - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman (The Women's Press Ltd.), 1984; F-184-9-0-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item33.
  - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman (large print edition), March 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item35.
  - Cameron, Anne - Dochters van Kopervrouw (Breda: De Geus en Edith van Dijk), 1992; F-184-9-0-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item37.
  - Chrystos - Dream On, 1991; F-184-9-0-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-51)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item38.
  - Chrystos - Firepower, 1995; F-184-9-0-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item39.
  - Chrystos - In Her I Am (second printing), September 1993; F-184-9-0-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item41.
  - Chrystos - Not Vanishing (first printing), May 1988; F-184-9-0-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item43.
  - Chrystos - Not Vanishing (secnd printing), August 1988; F-184-9-0-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item45.
  - Chrystos - Wilder Reis (Berlin: Orlanda Frauenverlag GmbH), 1997; F-184-9-0-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item46.
  - Creese, Gillian and Veronica Strong-Boag (editors) - British Columbia Reconsidered: Essays on Women, May 1992; F-184-9-0-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Strong-Boag, Veronica; Gillian Creese; Textual records
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item48.
  - Crossland, Jackie - Collateral Damage: The Tragedy of Medea, 1992; F-184-9-0-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item50.
  - Decter, Ann - Honour (first edition), 1996; F-184-9-0-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item52.
  - Decter, Ann - Paper, Scissors, Rock, September 1992; F-184-9-0-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 184-52)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item54.
  - Diamond, Sarah - Women's Labour History in British Columbia: A Bibliography, 1930-1948, 1980; F-184-9-0-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 184-53)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item56.
  - Dueck, Lynette - sing me no more, 1992; F-184-9-0-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 184-53)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item58.
  - Dykewomon, Elana - Beyond the Pale: A Novel (first printing), 1997; F-184-9-0-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 184-53)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item60.
  - Dykewomon, Elana - Beyond the Pale: A Novel (Winner, 1998 Lambda Literary Award), F-184-9-0-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 184-53)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item62.
  - Dykewomon, Elana - Sarahs Töchter (Berlin: Krug and Schadenberg), 1999; F-184-9-0-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 184-53)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item64.
  - Ellis, Megan - Surviving Procedures After A Sexual Assault (third edition), September 1989; F-184-9-0-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 184-53)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item66.
  - Faith, Karlene - Unruly Women: The Politics of Confinement and Resistance, December 1993; F-184-9-0-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 184-54)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item68.
  - Faith, Karlene - Unruly Women: The Politics of Confinement and Resistance (production copy), November 1993; F-184-9-0-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 184-54)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-184-item70.